{
    "subject": "resource/Adrian_P\u0103unescu",
    "predicate": "ontology/restingPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bellu_Cemetery",
    "human_readable": "Adrian P\u0103unescu's resting place is Bellu Cemetery.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882237911224365,
            "question": "Is Bellu Cemetery the resting place of Adrian P\u0103unescu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9604272842407227,
            "question": "Is Adrian P\u0103unescu buried in Bellu Cemetery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9130414128303528,
            "question": "What is the name of the cemetery where Adrian P\u0103unescu is laid to rest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891937732696533,
            "question": "In what cemetery does Adrian P\u0103unescu rest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.868482232093811,
            "question": "Can you tell me the location of Adrian P\u0103unescu's grave?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8030073046684265,
            "question": "Where is Adrian P\u0103unescu buried?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8017632365226746,
            "question": "What cemetery is associated with Adrian P\u0103unescu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567066550254822,
            "question": "Where can you find Adrian P\u0103unescu's final resting place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7294653058052063,
            "question": "What is known about Adrian P\u0103unescu's burial site?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7197118401527405,
            "question": "Adrian P\u0103unescu's final resting place is...?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adrian P\u0103unescu's resting place is Bellu Cemetery.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4162_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Adrian P\u0103unescu's burial site?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4162_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find Adrian P\u0103unescu's final resting place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4162_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What cemetery is associated with Adrian P\u0103unescu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4162_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4162_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the triple supports the statement:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Adrian Paunescu was buried, with military honours, in the Bellu Cemetery\" and also state that \"Paunescu will be buried at Bellu cemetery in Bucharest\". Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that Adrian P\u0103unescu's resting place is indeed the Bellu Cemetery."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Adrian Paunescu was buried at the Bellu Cemetery in Bucharest, which supports the statement that his resting place is Bellu Cemetery."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}